<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Governance on Carpentry at the University of Oslo</title><link>/governance/</link><description>Recent content in Governance on Carpentry at the University of Oslo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/governance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/governance/charter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/charter/</guid><description>Carpentry@UiO Charter # Organization # The Club board is made up of 6 members:
4 members elected for 2-years. 2 members are designated by the UiO Library Elections will be organized every year for renewing half of the elected members of the board (2 members).
The board will appoint a board chair, vice chair, communications officer and and secretary at the first meeting of the new board after the election.</description></item><item><title/><link>/governance/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/governance/intro/</guid><description>Introduction # Vision/Mission Statement # Carpentry@UiO is the UiO local relay of the international Carpentries organisation.
We are a group of volunteers from the University of Oslo and beyond. With support from the University of Oslo Library, we offer to PhD students, researchers and others at UiO, and beyond:
foundational coding and data science skills workshops from Software Carpentry and Data Carpentry Study Group events dedicated to open and reproducible science, knowledge sharing, re-enforcing learning or discussing new subjects for future workshops/lesson development educational development and networking opportunities with the possibility to become Certified Carpentries Instructor and/or Carpentries Instructor Trainer Our activities and community are open to any member of the UiO community including staff, faculty, and students, paid, and volunteer.</description></item></channel></rss>